Register of the Donald Marquand Dozer Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- LATIN AMERICA SUBJECT FILE, 1910-1980
  - Colombia
    - Education. Bibliography, mimeographed materials relating to the organization and function of the educational system, speech transcript (Jose Joaquim Salcedo), pamphlets and mimeographed and typescript reports including Lloyd H. Elliott and Rodolfo Low-Maus, "Report on the Organization of the Javeriana University" (prepared for the Ford Foundation), and the Republic of Colombia, "Conferencia sobre Educacion y Desarrollo Economico y Social en America Latina,", 1960-1965 (Folder 6-10)
    - Foreign relations. Speech transcript (Mauricio Obregon), seminar transcript, and a mimeographed report, "Colombia and the United States: A Briefing Paper," with an introduction by Reynold E. Carlson, 1960-1968 (Folder 11)
    - History. Serial issues (Popayan), 1960-1962 (Box 108, Folder 1-2)
    - Politics and government. Pamphlet (serial issue) by Luis Enrique Osorio, Los Derechos del Trabajador, and reports by Pat M. Holt, "Constitutional Development in Colombia," Ramiro de la Espriella, "Forma y Quebranto de la Oposicion en Colombia," and Alberto del Corral, "Camino a la Libertad,", 1937-1963 (Folder 3-4)
  - Costa Ricirca Statistical chart, newsletters, and a printed transcript (E) of a speech by Jose Figueres, 1950-1961 (Folder 5)
  - Cuba
    - General
      - General, Correspondence, including the State Department (Robert Woodward), 1960-1969. (Folder 6)
      - Non-printed material (Folder 7-8)
        - General, 1957-1972. Statistical chart, newsletters, interviews, a pamphlet compiled by Irwin Silber, The Cultural Congress of Havana State Dept. memorandum, resolutions of the Conferencia Comite Consultivo Secretariado Latino Americano de la Internacional Socialista (E/S), mimeographed reports, including "Economic Situation and Trends," an untitled report by Herbert Matthews, Antonio Casas Gonzalez, "El Azucar: Problema Economico Cubano," State Dept., "The Castro Regime in Cuba," and Universal Research and Consultants, Inc., "Communist Activities of the Cuban Rebels", (1968 january 4-11)
        - Gest, Sidney G., "Memorandum on the Cuban Situation," Typescript report and correspondence with Dr. Dozer, the State Dept., Paul Linebarger, Herbert L. Matthews and others, 1960-1961. (Folder 9)
      - Printed material
        - General, U.S. and Cuban serial issues, speech transcripts (Thomas Dodd and Fidel Castro), printed articles by Earl E.T. Smith, Harold Eugene Davis and Theodore Draper, and pamphlets, including The Declaration of Havana, and Como Cayo la Universidad, 1934-1980. (Folder 10-11)
        - Clippings (from U.S. sources), 1960-1974 (Folder 12)
        - Newsletters, 1961-1970 (Folder 13)
    - Foreign relations. Printed articles, hearing transcripts, statements by John Kennedy, Robert Sayre, and Sen. Carl T. Curtis, pamphlets and reports including Theodore Draper, "Cuba y la Politica Norteamericana,", 1961-1975 (Folder 14-15)
  - Dominican Republic. Letter, statistical chart, speech transcripts (Rafael L. Trujillo, Thomas C. Mann and J.W. Fulbright), pamphlets, newsletters ("Dateline: Dominican Republic"), flyer, bibliography, treaty text, reports, 1941-1980 (Box 109, Folder 1-2)
  - Ecuador
    - General
      - General
        - General. Pamphlets, newsletters, memorandum, 1961-1970 (Folder 3-4)
        - Clippings, 1963-1969 (Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 1958-1974 (Folder 6)
    - Economics. Flyer, reports of the Mision Andina en el Ecuador, and Francisco A. Salazar, Politica Habitacional, 1959-1969 (Folder 7-8)
    - Education. Bibliographies and pamphlets, 1963-1965 (Folder 9)
    - History. Pamphlet and printed articles (S), 1949-1962 (Folder 10)
    - Politics and government. Mimeographed report entitled "Projecto de Constitucion Politica del Estado Ecuatoriano que Presenta la Comision Especial Designada por el Directorio General del Partido Conservador,", undated (Folder 11)
  - El Salvador. Statistical chart, serial issue, flyers and several issues of a literary newspaper/joural entitled La Pajara Pinta, 1957-1971 (Folder 12-13)
  - Guatemala
    - General. Clippings, State Dept. memoranda, serial issue, printed and mimeographed reports (S)(E), newsletters, speech transcripts (Jacobo Arbenz Guzman, Miguel Ydigoras Fuentes and Carlos Urrutia-Aparicio), printed articles, letter to the editor, pamphlets, and extracts from an essay by Juan Jose Arevalo (E), 1947-1977 (Box 110, Folder 1-6)
    - Correspondence
      - General, 1968-1969 (Folder 7)
      - Urrutia-Aparicio, Carlos, Includes a letter from Miguel Ydigoras Fuentes, 1953-1967. (Folder 8-9)
  - Guyana (British Guiana). Clipping and printed State Dept. report, 1965 (Folder 10)
  - Haiti. Statistical chart, pamphlets, flyers, report, mimeographed letter from the Haitian Ambassador, Arthur Bonhomme. Includes Max L. Hudicourt, Haiti Faces Tomorrow's Peace, 1926-1975 (Folder 11)
  - Honduras. Tratados Internacionales, Vol. I, statistical chart, pamphlet, transcript, speech transcript and letter to Rafael Heliodoro Valle, 1953-1957 (Folder 12)
  - Jamaicirca Bank of Jamaica Bulletin, 1973 september (Folder 13)
  - Mexico
    - General
      - General, Clippings, pamphlets, bibliographies, statistical chart, and a mimeographed report by Barry Carr, "The Peculiarities of the Mexican North, 1880-1928", 1957-1979. (Box 111, Folder 1)
      - Serials, 1961-1969 (Folder 2-5)
    - Correspondence
      - General, Includes correspondence relating to a project to microfilm Mexican archives, 1960-1978. (Folder 6)
      - Hruneni, George A., Relates to research on Joel Poinsett, 1967-1972. (Folder 7)
    - Economics. Letter, conference materials, legal statutes, speech transcript (Ruben Gonzalez Sosa), printed article and reports, serial issue, a pamphlet by Faustino Ballve, Diez Lecciones de Economia, mimeographed report by General Electric (TEMPO), The Economic Potential of Mexico, and Philip B. Ellis, Changes in Agriculture and Settlement in Coastal Chiapas, Southern Mexico,", 1970-1975 (Folder 8-11)
    - Education. Booklets and a printed report, 1966-1973 (Box 112, Folder 1-2)
    - Foreign relations. Treaty texts, a printed article, a mimeographed booklet entitled Cooperative United States Mexico Border Studies, and photocopies of correspondence between Californian, Mexican and U.S. federal authorities (including Hiram Johnson and William H. Taft) relating to a 1911 border incident, 1911-1970 (Folder 3-4)
    - Politics and government. Newsletters, poem, and pamphlets, including a biography of Gustavo Diaz Ordaz, and speech transcripts and a printed article by Manuel M. Moreno, 1964-1970 (Folder 5-6)
  - Nicaragua. Statistical chart, treaty texts, newsletters, 1924-1979 (Folder 7)
  - Paraguay
    - General. Newsletter, clippings, book list, serial issues, statistical chart, correspondence, a promotional flyer for Andrei Sakharov, Progreso, Coexistencia y Libertad Intelectual, pamphlets including Cecilio Baez, Ensayo Sobre el Doctor Francia y la Dictadura en Sud-America, and a mimeographed report by John R. Hildebrand, "LAFTA and Paraguay: Economic and Social Development,", 1910-1973 (Folder 8-10)
    - Correspondence, 1944-1968 (Folder 11)
  - Peru
    - General
      - General
        - General, Newsletters, statistical chart, mimeographed report by the Comision de Ayuda Social, Concilio Nacional Evangelico de Peru (E) and "Carta Pastoral Colectiva del Episcopado Peruano sobre la Actividad Social y Politica en la Hora Presente" (S), with cover letter, 1962-1971. 1962-1971 (Folder 12)
        - Clippings, 1963-1974 (Folder 13)
        - Serial issues (Informe), 1969-1970 (Folder 14)
      - Correspondence
        - General, Includes Francisco Miro Quesada and Eudocio Ravines, 1963-1970. (Box 113, Folder 1)
        - Basadre, Jorge, 1965-1970 (Folder 2)
        - Beltran, Pedro, 1965-1969 (Folder 3)
    - Economics. Pamphlets, newsletters, press release, and notes for a speech (?) by Alexander Grobman, "Teoria y Proyecciones de la Reforma Agraria en el Peru,", 1948-1974 (Folder 4-6)
    - Foreign relations. Pamphlets, including transcripts of speeches by Pedro G. Beltran, and diplomatic exchanges between Peru and Colombia relating to Raul Haya de la Torre (all E), 1949-1963 (Folder 7)
    - History and Culture. Pamphlets, newsletters, newspaper reissue, (S only), 1879-1978 (Folder 8-9)
    - Politics. Newsletters (E & S), clippings, flyers, speech transcripts (Raul Haya de la Torre), flyers, mimeographed report, and pamphlets, including Oscar Bueno Tovar, Las Fuerzas Armadas y el APRA (radio broadcast), Fraternidad Aprista 1971 and Francisco Miro Quesada, La Ideologia de Accion Popular, 1960-1971 (Folder 10)
  - Puerto Rico. Statistical chart, flyers, card, printed article and reports, newspapers, pamphlet by J. Enamorado Cuesta, The Truth-Not Yet All the Truth-About Puerto Rico, and a collection of mimeographed letters from Gilberto Concepcion de Gracia, relating to Puerto Rican independence, 1948-1975 (Folder 11)
  - Uruguay
    - General
      - General
        - General, Political handbills, newsletter, flyers, serial issues, statistical chart, bibliography, memorandum, pamphlets and reports, including A Study of Conditions Necessary to Assure Political Defense, 1947-1969. (Folder 12-13)
        - Clippings, 1963-1973 (Box 114, Folder 1-2)
      - Correspondence, 1963-1972 (Folder 3)
    - Economics. Newsletters, State Dept. memoranda, chart, letters, pamphlets, including Julio Herrera Vargas, Como se Agrava la Crisis Nacional, and mimeographed reports entitled "Guia de la Legislacion Labor y de los Seguros Sociales", "Summary of CIDE Report," Rogelio Cheroni San Roman, "Informe General de las Relaciones del Uruguay con la OIT", and Alejandro Vegh Villegas, "El Progreso Tecnologico y la Economia Politica,", 1961-1976 (Folder 4-8)
  - Venezuela
    - General
      - General
        - General, Bibliography, statistical chart, speech transcripts (Romulo Betancourt and Arturo Uslar Pietri) (S)(E), a biography of Raul Leoni, clippings relating to President Carlos Andres Perez' visit to the United States, flyers, a report by Arturo Uslar Pietri, "The City of Gold and the City of Justice", and pamphlets, including Venezuela 1961, 1949-1977. (Folder 9-11)
        - Clippings, 1963-1977 (Folder 12)
        - Newsletters
          - Actualidad Venezolana (includes issues of a different series printed in English entitled Venezuelan Highlights, 1962-1964 (Box 115, Folder 1-2)
          - Venezuela Now, 1977-1978 (Folder 3-4)
        - Serial issues (E)(S), 1956-1974 (Folder 5-6)
      - Correspondence
        - General, 1962-1976 (Folder 7)
        - Betancourt, Romulo, 1960-1962 (Folder 8)
        - Casas Gonzalez, Antonio, 1960-1966 (Folder 9)
        - Planas-Suarez, Simon, 1963 (Folder 10)
    - Culture. Pamphlets, including six numbers of a series "Coleccion 'Manuel Felipe Rugeles'", 1961-1968 (Folder 11-12)
    - Economics
      - General
        - General
          - General, Annual reports, newsletters, pamphlets, reports, memorandum, serial issue, printed and mimeographed reports by the Federacion Venezolana de Camaras y Asociaciones de Comercio y Produccion, and a mimoegraphed report by the Camara de Comercio de Maracaibo, 1950-1970.
            - 1950-1963 (Folder 13-15)
            - 1964-1970 (Box 116, Folder 1-4)
          - Conference of the Caribbean (13th), University of Florida, Gainesville, List of participants, and mimeographed reports, 1962 december 6-8. (Folder 5-7)
        - ACCION (Community Action in Latin America). Staff descriptions, reports, newsletters, flyers, clippings, letters, application forms, 1960-1965 (Folder 8-9)
      - Oil. Creole Petroleum Company annual report, pamphlet by the Corporacion Venezolana de Petroleo, Sintesis Historica de la Industria del Petroleo en Venezuela, printed article by Arturo Uslar Pietri, "Sembrar el Petroleo: Veinticinco Anos de Una Consigna," State Dept. report and serial issues (Revista Shell), 1953-1962 (Folder 10-12)
    - Education. Pamphlets, memorandum, letter, mimeographed reports, 1949-1963 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - History. Serial issue and pamphlets, 1964-1974 (Folder 2-3)
    - Politics. Serials/flyers (Trinchera and Pueblo y Revolucion), flyer, special tabloid issued by the Gobierno Revolucionario de los E.E.U.U. de Venezuela, "Realizaciones de la Revolucion de Octubre," mimeographed reports, "Leftist Insurgency" and "Mensaje de Accion Venezolana Independiente a la Nacion", and pamphlets, including Planteamiento de Pompeyo Marquez en la Polemica Iniciada por Clarin, Rafael Caldera, Revolucion y Juventud, Defensa de la Constitucionalidad, and La Actitud del Socialcristianismo en Defensa de la Democracia, 1946-1965 (Folder 4-5)
- SUBJECT FILE, 1893-1980
  Correspondence, reports, memoranda, clippings, newsletters, speech transcripts, press releases, pamphlets, flyers, notes, resolutions, serial issues, and other miscellany. Arranged by subject.
  - General
    - Non-printed material. Flyers, mimeographed reports including Richard H. Sanger, "Life Cycle of a Typical Revolt," and "The Age of Insurgency," and S.I. Hayakawa, "Radical Revenge Against the FBI?", and a printed pamphlet by Francis Parker Yockey, The Proclamation of London of The European Liberation Front, 1965-1978 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Printed material. Clippings, pamphlets, flyer, speech transcripts (includes Dwight Eisenhower and Herbert Hoover), newsletter and reprints, 1953-1977 (Folder 7-8)
  - Africa
    - General, Mimeographed report, pamphlet, reprint, map, and material relating to Moise Tshombe, 1944-1969. (Folder 9)
    - American-African Affairs Association
      - General, Flyers, newsletters, letters, miscellany, 1966-1978. (Folder 10)
      - Memoranda and minutes, 1965-1972 (Folder 11-12)
      - Reports, Printed pamphlets and mimeographed reports including Walter Darnell Jacobs, "A Constitution for Rhodesia," and "Report on Rhodesia: April 1967", 1966-1973. (Box 118, Folder 1-3)
  - Canada. Pamphlet and a short printed report, 1964-1969 (Folder 4)
  - Communism and anti-communism
    - General, 1921-1979. Speech transcripts (William E. Jenner), serials issued by the Progressive Labor Party (Challenge), press release, newsletter, flyers, letters, printed and mimeographed reports, map, pamphlets, printed article and clippings (Folder 5-7)
    - Bunche, Ralph. Clipping and a mimeographed report with cover letter by Archibald Roosevelt, 1959 (Folder 8)
    - Oppenheimer, J. Robert. Clippings and form letters relating to Harvard appointment, 1956-1958 (Folder 9)
  - Defense. Naval Reserve training handout, clipping, form letter, speech transcript (William E. Jenner), pamphlets, flyers, newsletter, 1957-1980 (Folder 10)
  - Economics
    - General
      - Non-printed material, Letters, speech transcripts, notes, newsletters, miscellany, mimeographed reports, 1956-1979. (Folder 11-13)
      - Printed material, Flyers, pamphlets, newsletters, 1943-1979. (Box 119, Folder 1-8)
    - Pepperdine College Seminars
      - Letters, agenda and mimeographed reports, 1965. (Folder 9-10)
      - Letter and agenda, 1966. (Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, 1967.
      - Correspondence and pamphlet, 1969.
    - Political Economy Conference, San Francisco, Correspondence, notes and conference materials, 1962 august (Folder 12)
  - Education. Relates predominantly to educational controversies and student unrest in the late, 1960's-early 1970's
    - General
      - Correspondence, 1951-1973 (Box 120, Folder 1-2)
      - Non-printed material, Speech transcripts (including Sen. William E. Jenner), resume, notes, form letters, statements, bibliographies, interview with Bruno Bettelheim, newsletters, flyers, form letters (including Ronald Reagan), and reports by the Young Americans for Freedom and Alexander W. Astin (American Council on Education), 1952-1973. (Folder 3-5)
      - Printed material, Clippings, speech transcript (Max Rafferty), reports, bibliography, newsletters, pamphlets, policy statements, printed article, 1952-1979. (Folder 6-10)
    - Cornell Alumni Association for Balanced Education
      - General. Newsletters
        - 1960-1970 (Folder 11-13)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 121, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence (J.D. Tuller), 1969-1973 (Folder 2)
    - Foreign Policy Conference for Educators, Clippings, schedule, correspondence and conference materials, 1967 february (Folder 3)
    - Intercollegiate Society of Individualists. Pamphlets, serial issue, flyer, newsletters, letters, 1959-1964 (Folder 4)
    - University of California
      - General
        - Correspondence and memoranda, Includes the Governor's office and the U.C. Board of Regents, 1967-1973. (Folder 5)
        - Non-printed material
          - General, Lists of regents, minutes, position statements, newsletters and flyers, 1967-1978. (Folder 6-8)
          - Academic Senate. Minutes, resolutions, reports, clipping, 1966-1970 (Folder 9-10)
        - Notes, circa 1969-1970 (Folder 11)
        - Printed material, Newsletters and clippings, primarily relating to U.C. Santa Barbara, including an article by Chancellor Vernon I. Cheadle, 1966-1970. (Folder 12-14)
      - Regents Lectureship Series. Correspondence with Alberto Benegas Lynch and others, 1970 (Box 122, Folder 1)
      - Reserve Officers Training Corps (R.O.T.C.)
        - Correspondence, Includes Rep. Charles M. Teague, 1968-1972. (Folder 2)
        - Non-printed material, Statements drafted by Dr. Dozer, membership lists (Friends of the R.O.T.C.), newsletter, flyers, resolutions, miscellany, 1968-1976. 1968-1976 (Folder 3-4)
        - Notes (Folder 5)
        - Printed material. Predominantly clippings from Santa Barbara and campus newspapers; also includes a printed report by the UCSB Department of Political Science, Army R.O.T.C.: Reassessment of the Curriculum, 1967-1972 (Folder 6-7)
    - University Professors for Academic Order. Form letters, newsletters, flyers and miscellany, 1970-1979. (Folder 8)
  - Egypt (Suez Crisis). Pamphlets, printed article and press release, 1955-1956 (Folder 9)
  - England. Reprint and serials, 1957-1960 (Folder 10)
  - Foundation for Economic Education
    - General, Seminar materials, newsletters and flyers, 1961-1977. (Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1961-1970 (Folder 12-13)
  - History
    - General
      - Non-printed material. Letter, press release, statements by Senator John M. Butler, a mimeographed report by Theodore Ropp, "Military Historical Scholarship Since 1937," and notes (relating to the accession of Chester A. Arthur to the presidency), 1949-1969 (Box 123, Folder 1-2)
      - Printed material. Flyers, reprints, printed articles, maps and a section from a Michigan newspaper describing Siberian penal settlements, 1893-1976 (Folder 3-4)
    - Princeton Conference in American Civilization: Religion in American Life, Mimeographed reports, outlines, bibliographies and a printed pamphlet, 1953-1954. (Folder 5-6)
    - Washington Historians Group. Membership lists, meeting announcements and correspondence, including a letter to Vladimir Bazykin of the Soviet Embassy, extending a speaking invitation, 1942-1944 (Folder 7)
  - Institute for Humane Studies
    - General, Flyers, annual reports, pamphlets by F.A. Harper, F.A. von Hayek, and others, speech transcript (F.A. von Hayek), 1951-1979. (Folder 8-11)
    - Correspondence and memoranda, Primarily Kenneth Templeton and F.A. Harper, 1966-1979. (Folder 12-13)
  - Japan. Newsletter, clippings, pamphlet, 1973-1978 (Folder 14)
  - Judaism, Zionism, and anti-semitism. Correspondence, newsletter, book lists and reviews, speech transcript (Curtis B. Dall), serial issue, flyer, book excerpt, meeting report and printed booklets by Paul Rassinier and Austin J. App, 1955-1978 (Box 124, Folder 1-3)
  - Laos. Letters and mimeographed newsletter series by Howard Lewin, 1965-1969 (Folder 4-5)
  - Maryland
    - General
      - General, Flyers, newsletters, agenda, speech transcripts (Albert C. Ritchie), annual report, mimeographed reports, bibliographies, and statistical reports, 1924-1975. (Folder 6-7)
      - Radio broadcast transcripts ("Annapolis Index"), Relates primarily to Maryland history, 1955-1958. (Folder 8)
    - Regional Planning Council
      - General, Newsletter, pamphlet, speech transcript, legal statutes, membership lists, by-laws, and mimeographed reports by Walter C. Boyd, 1971-1975. (Folder 9-10)
      - "Appendix to Master Planning Study for Port of Baltimore, " 1974. Mimeographed report, 1974-1990
        - Parts I-II (Folder 11-13)
        - Parts III-IV (Box 125, Folder 1-5)
  - McCarthy, Joseph. Clippings, newsletters, speech (William E. Jenner), letter from Mrs. Jean McCarthy, flyer, 1954-1957 (Folder 6)
  - Mont Pelerin Society
    - General
      - General, Directories, speech transcript, form letters, meeting reports and agenda, letters, miscellany and mimeographed reports, 1971-1980. (Folder 7-8)
      - Newsletters, 1972-1980 (Folder 9-10)
    - Caracas meeting, 1969
      - General. Organizational materials (Folder 11)
      - Reports
        - A-G (Folder 12)
        - H-V (Box 126, Folder 1-2)
    - Munich meeting, 1970
      - General. Organizational materials and correspondence (Folder 3)
      - Reports (Folder 4-5)
    - Montreux meeting, 1972
      - General. Organizational materials (Folder 6)
      - Reports (Folder 7)
    - Guatemala meeting, 1973
      - General. Organizational materials (Folder 8)
      - Reports (Folder 9-10)
    - Brussels meeting, 1974
      - General (Folder 11)
      - Reports (Folder 12-13)
    - Scotland meeting, Primarily organizational materials, 1976. (Folder 14)
  - Nuclear energy. Clipping, pamphlets, speech transcript (William E. Jenner), circa 1957-1975 (Folder 15)
  - Portugal. Pamphlets, map and flyer, 1937-1939 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Shockley, William. Newsletters, 1965-1975 (Folder 2-4)
  - South Africirca SEE ALSO: Africa/American-African Affairs Association
    - General, Flyer, newsletters and correspondence, 1967-1978. (Folder 5)
    - Newsletters (RSA World), 1967-1979 (Folder 6-10)
  - Spain. Pamphlet, reprint and serials, 1953-1969 (Folder 11)
  - Sudan. Mimeographed report by the Stanford Research Institute, "National Development Planning,", 1974 (Folder 12)
  - Taxation and government spending. Hearing transcript, form letter, mimeographed report, press release, flyers, 1971-1975 (Folder 13)
  - United Nations. Printed article, copy of Dumbarton Oaks proposals, newsletters, charter, pamphlets, speech transcript (William F. Knowland), 1945-1977 (Folder 14)
  - United States - Bicentennial celebration, 1976
    - General, Correspondence, including letters from Ronald Reagan, 1968-1978. (Box 128, Folder 1-12)
    - National
      - General
        - Non-printed material, Directories, bibliographies, flyers, speech transcript, memorandum, mimeographed report. Includes materials from the People's Bicentennial Commission, 1970-1977. (Folder 13)
        - Printed material, Pamphlets newsletter, map and miscellany, 1962-1977. (Box 129, Folder 1)
      - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission. Speech transcripts (Gerald Ford, Richard Nixon), letter, printed reports, chart, newsletter, press releases, directories, form letter, flyer, pamphlet, 1969-1976 (Folder 2-3)
    - California
      - General, Report, form letter, press releases, minutes, map, clippings, resolutions, 1968-1976. (Folder 4)
      - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission
        - Non-printed material, Reports, notes, resolutions, directories, minutes, newsletters, 1970-1977. (Folder 5-6)
        - Printed material, Newsletter, pamphlets, flyers, clippings, miscellany, 1973-1977. (Folder 7-8)
    - Massachusetts. Revolutionary War Bicentennial Commission
      - General, Pamphlets and a program, 1968-1971. (Box 130, Folder 1)